{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"4.32/2",
			"answer":"4.32/2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.216/0.6",
			"answer":"0.216/0.6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"86.8/7",
			"answer":"86.8/7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"590/0.005",
			"answer":"590/0.005",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"580/0.4",
			"answer":"580/0.4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"120/0.04",
			"answer":"120/0.04",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"61.8/0.006",
			"answer":"61.8/0.006",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"280/0.005",
			"answer":"280/0.005",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"4.26/0.06",
			"answer":"4.26/0.06",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"28.4/0.04",
			"answer":"28.4/0.04",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.366/0.03",
			"answer":"0.366/0.03",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"30.6/3",
			"answer":"30.6/3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"750/0.2",
			"answer":"750/0.2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"5.4/0.09",
			"answer":"5.4/0.09",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"89.6/0.7",
			"answer":"89.6/0.7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}